<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Topic//EN" "../dtd/technicalContent/dtd/topic.dtd">
<topic id="id151RC0J0EEK" xml:lang="EN">
<title>Compathy ContentGrasp SX</title>
<shortdesc>Mind Your Own Business</shortdesc>
<prolog>
<author>Sam Won</author>
<copyright><copyryear year="2015"/><copyrholder>Compathy Inc.</copyrholder>
</copyright>
<permissions view="Author"/></prolog>
<topic id="topic-15-1DFB7DF6">
<title>Preface</title>
<body>
<p>Congratulations on your purchase of the ContentGrasp SX headset.
This revolutionary device will significantly improve the quality of
your technical documentation without implementing an additional work
step. During the normal review, the reviewers or test persons can
check</p>
<ul>
<li>how comprehensible individual passages were;</li>
<li>how carefully individual passages were read;</li>
<li>which passages needed to be read repeatedly.</li>
</ul>
<p>This information is recorded by the headset and analyzed by intelligent
software using a sophisticated algorithm.</p>
<p>The result enables detailed, systematic improvement of the comprehensibility
of technical documentation at an unprecedented level.</p>
</body>
</topic>
<topic id="topic-15-1DFBA984">
<title>Safety Informations</title>
<body>
<section><title>Radio Interference</title><p>Strong static, electric
or high-frequency fields (radio systems, mobile phones, microwave
ovens) can impair the function of the device and distort the results.
Try to stay as far as possible from interfering appliances.</p></section>
<section><title>Headache</title><p>In extremely rare cases, prolonged
use of the ContentGrasp SX headset can cause headache and increased
irritability. Avoid sessions of more than four hours, and regularly
take breaks.</p></section>
<section><title>Skin Irritation</title><p>Skin irritation can occur
at the contact points during prolonged  use. Use the supplied contact
gel to protect your skin.</p></section>
</body>
</topic>
<topic id="topic-16-1DFC05C0">
<title>Product Scope</title>
<body>
<p>The ContentGrasp SX headset comprises the following components:</p>
<ul>
<li>ContentGrasp SX headset</li>
<li>ContentGrasp SX analysis software</li>
<li>Compathy ContentGrasp SX cable remote control</li>
<li>These instructions </li>
<li>One bottle of ContentGrasp SX contact gel</li>
</ul>
</body>
</topic>
<topic id="topic-17-1DFC62B5">
<title>System Requirements</title>
<body>
<ul>
<li>Intel Core 2 Duo 2.2 GHz or similar AMD CPU</li>
<li>2 GB RAM</li>
<li>Windows 7/Windows 8</li>
<li>8 GB free hard disk space</li>
<li>Free USB interface</li>
</ul>
</body>
</topic>
<topic id="topic-18-1DFC73DC">
<title>Use</title>
<body>
<p>Put the ContentGrasp SX headset on like normal earphones. Slightly
pull the two sides of the headband to adjust the headset to the size
of your head.</p>
<p>Make sure that the two ear pads comfortably encompass your ears.
This ensures that the sensors on the headband are positioned correctly,
and your brain waves can be analyzed effectively.</p>
<p>Subsequently, open the caps on the right and left ear pad and extract
the temple sensors as far as they will go. Firmly press the sensors
to your temples and pull the attached handles. Optionally, you can
apply some contact gel to your temples.</p>
<p>To avoid impairment of the sensor performance, keep your hair out
of the way between your temples and the sensors.</p>
<p>To activate the headset, press the On/Off button on the cable remote
control. You can also activate the headset via the ContentGrasp SX
icon in the systray of your computer.</p>
<p>Open the document to be evaluated. Confirm the dialog that opens
up automatically by clicking "Start". Thus, the recording will begin,
and you should start reading the document.</p>
<p>You can always interrupt the recording with the cable remote control,
which however will also minimize the document.</p>
</body>
</topic>
</topic>
